Guide to the Pat Williams Papers 1979-1997
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1979-1996; Series XI; 1.0 linear foot
  - Pat Williams receiving the National Endowment for the Humanities award, Oct. 1985; 239(XI):54 (Box 158/54)
  - Group around banner beginning of the first "Superintendents' Trek" at Glacier, 1985; 239(XI):55 (Box 158/55)
  - Dr. John Sellers, Stan Kimmitt, Ralph Regula, Pat Williams at MHD, Butte, undated; 239(XI):56 (Box 158/56)
  - Pat Williams at Captain Cook Canary, Iverness, Montana, May 1995; 239(XI):57 (Box 158/57)
  - Pat Williams with unidentified woman in front of Capital, undated; 239(XI):58 (Box 158/58)
  - Pat Williams meeting with Japanese officials in Tokyo, undated; 239(XI):59 (Box 158/59)
  - Nashville, TN, 1987; 239(XI):60 (Box 158/60)
  - Pat Williams and Marvin Hamlish, undated; 239(XI):61 (Box 158/61)
  - Pat Williams shaking Marvin Hamlish's hand, undated; 239(XI):62 (Box 158/62)
  - Sec. of Education, Pat Williams, and Bill Ford, Feb. 1993; 239(XI):63 (Box 158/63)
  - Hillary Clinton and Pat Williams, Feb. 23, 1993; 239(XI):64 (Box 158/64)
  - Hilary Clinton addressing audience, Great Falls, 1993; 239(XI):65 (Box 158/65)
  - Hilary Clinton receiving applause, Great Falls, 1993; 239(XI):66 (Box 158/66)
  - People mingling on stage behind panel table, Great Falls, 1993; 239(XI):67 (Box 158/67)
  - Members of panel standing at table, Great Falls, 1993; 239(XI):68 (Box 158/68)
  - Pat Williams and unidentified man with Stacy and Becki, April 8, 1993; 239(XI):69 (Box 158/69)
  - Pat Williams between Stacy and Becki, Fort Harrison, Montana, April 8, 1993; 239(XI):70 (Box 158/70)
  - Pat Williams and Sec. Reich, DOL, undated; 239(XI):71 (Box 158/71)
  - Berle Anthony, Mike Synar, and Pat Williams, undated; 239(XI):72 (Box 158/72)
  - President Clinton shaking Pat Williams hand, undated; 239(XI):73 (Box 158/73)
  - Pat Williams with three unidentified women, Yellowstone, Aug. 1996; 239(XI):74 (Box 158/74)
  - "NEPA Walk," Pat Williams with woman, Yellowstone, Aug. 1996; 239(XI):75 (Box 158/75)
  - "NEPA Walk," Pat Williams standing with woman, Yellowstone, Aug. 1996; 239(XI):76 (Box 158/76)
  - Picture of Pat Williams Congressional Field Office Window, Butte, undated; 239(XI):77 (Box 158/77)
  - Pat Williams with eight unidentified librarians, 1984; 239(XI):78 (Box 158/78)
  - Pat Williams with eight unidentified librarians, 1984; 239(XI):79 (Box 158/79)
  - Pat Williams speaking at a podium, undated; 239(XI):80 (Box 158/80)
  - Jim Watt, Sec. of Interior, at an Interiror Committee hearing, undated; 239(XI):81 (Box 158/81)
  - Pat Williams at Hospital Administration Meeting, Missoula, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):82 (Box 158/82)
  - Pat Williams at Hospital Administration Meeting, Missoula, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):83 (Box 158/83)
  - Pat Williams meeting Pope John Paul, undated; 239(XI):84 (Box 158/84)
  - National ALF-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):85 (Box 158/85)
  - Montana Banner at National ALF-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):86 (Box 158/86)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):87 (Box 158/87)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):88 (Box 158/88)
  - Montana's Representation at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):89 (Box 158/89)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):90 (Box 158/90)
  - Pat Williams at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):91 (Box 158/91)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):92 (Box 158/92)
  - Montana banner at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):93 (Box 158/93)
  - Montana banner at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):94 (Box 158/94)
  - Sigh displaying "Beware of REGAN'S REVOLUTION," National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):95 (Box 158/95)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):96 (Box 158/96)
  - Transport Workers' Union banner, National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):97 (Box 158/97)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):98 (Box 158/98)
  - UAW Signs at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):99 (Box 158/99)
  - Pat Williams talking to unidentified man at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):100 (Box 158/100)
  - Montana State Banner at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):101 (Box 158/101)
  - Montana State Banner at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):102 (Box 158/102)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):103 (Box 158/103)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):104 (Box 158/104)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):105 (Box 158/105)
  - Looking down at the signs for National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):106 (Box 158/106)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):107 (Box 158/107)
  - Pat Williams at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):108 (Box 158/108)
  - Montana State Banner at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):109 (Box 158/109)
  - Row of flags and Blimp in air above them at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):110 (Box 158/110)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):111 (Box 158/111)
  - View of crowd at National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):112 (Box 158/112)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):113 (Box 158/113)
  - National AFL-CIO Rally, Washington, D.C., undated; 239(XI):114 (Box 158/114)
  - VFW Luncheon at Roma's Restaurant, Washington, D.C., March 5 1979; 239(XI):115 (Box 158/115)
  - Karl Borchers, Cal Murphy, Harold Gerke, Herb Walberg, Jay Robertson, C.H. Steele, Pat Williams, Feb. 1989; 239(XI):116 (Box 158/116)
  - House Speaker Jim Wright with Pat and Carol, Missoula, undated; 239(XI):117 (Box 158/117)
  - Pat Williams and Mike Lowry on steps of capital, undated; 239(XI):118 (Box 158/118)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with man at St. Patrick's Day Luncheon, Washington, D.C., March 1987; 239(XI):119 (Box 158/119)
  - Pat Williams watching President Regan shake a man's hand at St. Patrick's Day Luncheon, March 1987; 239(XI):120 (Box 158/120)
  - Pat Williams in "prison" surrounded by guards, Glasgow, undated; 239(XI):121 (Box 158/121)
  - Pat Williams "under arrest," Glasgow, undated; 239(XI):122 (Box 158/122)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with NYC Mayor at Congressional Arts Caucus, NYC, April 1987; 239(XI):123 (Box 158/123)
  - Three photos from meeting about Boxing Reform efforts, undated; 239(XI):124 (Box 158/124)
  - Two pictures of Pat Williams with Kathleen Turner, Morgan Freeman, Kevin Kline, and Joseph Papp at Arts Caucus, June 12, 1990; 239(XI):125 (Box 158/125)
  - Arts Caucus, June 12, 1990; 239(XI):126 (Box 158/126)
  - Pat Williams with Spring Creek Community School, on steps of the Capital, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):127 (Box 158/127)
  - Austin Grahm, Neva Bear, Pat Williams, and Leann Ohs, Feb. 25, 1993; 239(XI):128 (Box 159/1)
  - Joint Conference Committee, Kennedy, Egleton, Ratchford, Pat Williams and many unidentified, undated; 239(XI):129 (Box 159/2)
  - Caehlo, Carr, Russ, and unidentified man on board airplane, undated; 239(XI):130 (Box 159/3)
  - Pat Williams with Secretary Joe Califano, Health and Human Services, undated; 239(XI):131 (Box 159/4)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with Floyd Paterson, Ed Beard watching, undated; 239(XI):132 (Box 159/5)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with Japanese Prime Minister, standing next to Mike Mansfield, early eighties; 239(XI):133 (Box 159/6)
  - Pat Williams sitting nest to Mike Mansfield, many unidentified Japanese and American officials, early eighties; 239(XI):134 (Box 159/7)
  - Pat Williams with a group of students, undated; 239(XI):135 (Box 159/8)
  - Pat Williams with Paul Simon, Governor Carlos Romero Bancelo, unidentified Puerto Rican delegate, Puerto Rico, undated; 239(XI):136 (Box 159/9)
  - John Murray, John Melcher, Pat Williams, Mike Fairbanks, North American Indian Days, Browning, Montana, July 9, 1983; 239(XI):137 (Box 159/10)
  - Pat Williams speaking at Press Conference regarding passage of the Health Care Reform Bill, undated; 239(XI):138 (Box 159/11)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with President Clinton at Press Conference for Health Care Reform bill, many unidentified people, undated; 239(XI):139 (Box 159/12)
  - President Clinton, Pat Williams and three unidentified people pose for picture at press conference for Health Care Reform bill, undated; 239(XI):140 (Box 159/13)
  - President Clinton, Pat Williams and three unidentified people pose for picture at press conference for Health Care Reform bill, undated; 239(XI):141 (Box 159/14)
  - Hilary Clinton visiting Pat Williams's office, Feb. 23, 1993; 239(XI):142 (Box 159/15)
  - Hilary Clinton speaking to Pat Williams, undated; 239(XI):143 (Box 159/16)
  - Pat Williams leaning towards Mike Mansfield, Mansfield smiling, undated; 239(XI):144 (Box 159/17)
  - Pat Williams staff, undated; 239(XI):145 (Box 159/18)
  - Pat Williams staff, Oct. 1987; 239(XI):146 (Box 159/19)
  - Pat Williams with staff member Grey, March 1988; 239(XI):147 (Box 159/20)
  - Pat Williams staff, March 1988; 239(XI):148 (Box 159/21)
  - Pat Williams staff, 1989; 239(XI):149 (Box 159/22)
  - Pat Williams staff, July 1991; 239(XI):150 (Box 159/23)
  - Pat Williams shaking hands with Tommy Hearns, 1987; 239(XI):151 (Box 159/24)
  - Pat Williams speaking to President Clinton, signed by Clinton, undated; 239(XI):152 (Box 159/25)
  - Pat Williams with Betty Ford and Rosslyn Carter, Health Care Reform Luncheon, March 1994; 239(XI):153 (Box 159/26)
  - Pat Williams with Joseph Red Thunder, Sept. 24, 1992; 239(XI):154 (Box 159/27)
  - Pat Williams and President Clinton shaking hands, undated; 239(XI):155 (Box 159/28)
  - St. Helena Cathedral, undated; 239(XI):156 (Box 159/29)
  - Pat Williams and Thomas P. O'Neill, undated; 239(XI):157 (Box 159/30)
  - Pat Williams, Thomas P. O'Neill, and unidentified man and woman, undated; 239(XI):158/ (Box 159/31)
  - Thomas P. O'Neill with unidentified man and woman, undated; 239(XI):159/ (Box 159/32)
  - Pat Williams and Thomas P. O'Neill, picture accompanied by The Montana Democrat, The Washington Post, The New Republic, and prepared remarks, 1983-1985; 239(XI):160 (Box 159/33)
  - Pat Williams at dedication of the MHP facility in Butte, April, 1981; 239(XI):161 (Box 159/34)
  - Pat Williams speaking at the dedication of the MHP facility in Butte, April 1981; 239(XI):162 (Box 159/35)
  - Vice President Al Gore and Pat Williams shaking hands, Feb. 17, 1993; 239(XI):163 (Box 159/36)
  - MC Beverage, Pat Williams and Carter Mollgaard, Feb. 1994; 239(XI):164 (Box 159/37)
  - Pat Williams at MC Beverage, Miles City, Feb. 1994; 239(XI):165 (Box 159/38)
  - Six photos from Blackfoot Medical Center Fire, undated; 239(XI):166 (Box 159/39)
  - Two photos of Terry Mimnaugh and her Jeanette Rankin statue, 1985; 239(XI):167 (Box 159/40)
  - Six photos of Jeanette Rankin, various dates, undated; 239(XI):168 (Box 159/41)
  - Montana Governor Ted Schwinden speaking at the unveiling of the Rankin Statue at U.S. Capital Rotunda, May 1, 1985; 239(XI):169 (Box 159/42)
  - Max Baucus speaking at the Jeanette Rankin Statue unveiling, U.S. Capital Rotunda, May 1, 1985; 239(XI):170 (Box 159/43)
  - Unidentified speaker at the Jeanette Rankin statue unveiling, U.S. Capital Rotunda, May 1, 1985; 239(XI):171 (Box 159/44)
  - Jeanette Rankin statue in U.S. Capital, undated; 239(XI):172 (Box 159/45)
  - Mt. Gov. Ted Schwinden, Tom Kinney, Thomas P. O'Niell, Jr., Terry Mimnaugh unveiling statue, U.S. Capital Rotunda, May 1, 1985; 239(XI):173 (Box 159/46)
  - Max Baucus, Ted Schwinden, Terry Mimnaugh, Thomas P. O'Niell, Jr., Ron Marlenee, John Melcher, and Pat Williams, four photos, May 1, 1985; 239(XI):174 (Box 159/47)
  - Montana Wilderness tour, Sept. 1987; 239(XI):175 (Box 159/48)
  - Trapper Creek Job Corps, Bitterroot NF Photobook, 20 photos, Jan. 19, 1994; 239(XI):176 (Box 159/49)
  - Pat Williams with four unidentified men, undated; 239(XI):177 (Box 159/50)
  - Pat Williams sitting next to Pete, with note, Jan. 1988; 239(XI):178 (Box 159/51)
  - Pat Williams and unidentified others smiling for picture, with note, Jan. 1988; 239(XI):179 (Box 159/52)
  - Unidentified group, "shuttle shot" written on back, undated; 239(XI):180 (Box 159/53)
  - Large group in banquet room, 1987 reunion, 239(XI):181 (Box 159/54)
  - Pat Williams with arm around unidentified woman, four other unidentified people, posing for picture, 1987 reunion, 239(XI):182 (Box 159/55)
  - Pat Williams with tow unidentified men standing at a bar, 1987 reunion, 239(XI):183 (Box 159/56)
  - Three unidentified women posing for picture, 1987 reunion, 239(XI):184 (Box 159/57)
  - Unidentified man and woman sitting at a table, 1987 reunion, 239(XI):185 (Box 159/58)
  - Wilderness Designation Protest, "Montanans for Multiple Use," Columbia Falls, Montana, (multiple photographs), undated (Box-folder 159/59)
  - President Clinton giving speech, undated; 239(XI):186 (Box 160OS)
  - Pat Williams and Jim Rowe shaking hands, undated; 239(XI):187 (Box 160OS)